http://www.novusglass.com/us/en/legal

United States
CanadaEnglishFrançais  SpainEnglishEspañol  Australia  Ireland  New Zealand
Country | Language
Canada (English)  Canada (Français)  United States  Spain (English)  Spain (Español)  Australia  Ireland  New Zealand
Contact NOVUS Glass
1-800-77-NOVUS
United States
CanadaEnglishFrançais  SpainEnglishEspañol  Australia  Ireland  New Zealand
Legal
HomeLegal
Internet Terms of Use
Terms of Use
The following states the Terms of Use under which you may use this Web Site. Please read carefully. By accessing, browsing, using or downloading materials from this Web Site you agree to follow and be bound by these terms and conditions. Changes to this Web Site and these Terms of Use may be made at any time and without notice and you should visit this page periodically to review the Terms of Use, as you will be bound by such changes. Only Authorized Users may access the password-protected, secure section of this Web Site.
Copyright
The copyright in all material provided on this Web Site ("Material") is held by NOVUS Franchising Inc. or by the original creator of the Material. Unauthorized use of the Material may violate copyright, trademark, and other laws. Permission is granted to you to view, distribute and download a single copy of the Material on this Web site solely for your personal, non-commercial use, provided you do not modify the Material and you retain all copyright and other proprietary notices contained in the Material. You may not otherwise copy, reproduce, distribute, download or display, transmit the Material in any form or by any means without the permission of NOVUS Franchising Inc. If you do not comply with any of the Terms of Use, your permission to use the Material automatically terminates. Upon termination, you must destroy any downloaded and printed Material.
Trademarks
The trademarks, trade names, service marks and logos ("trademarks") found on this Web Site are proprietary to NOVUS Franchising Inc.and their use and reproduction is strictly prohibited. Nothing on this Web Site should be construed as granting, by implication, estoppel, or otherwise, any license or right to use any trademark displayed on the Web Site, without the written permission of the trademark owner. NOVUS Franchising Inc. aggressively enforces its intellectual property rights to the fullest extent of the law. The NOVUS name and logo is proprietary to NOVUS Franchising Inc. and may not be used in any way, including in advertising or publicity pertaining to distribution of materials on this Web Site, without prior, written permission. NOVUS Franchising Inc. prohibits use of the NOVUS name and logo as a "hot" link to any site unless establishment of such a link is approved in advance by NOVUS Franchising Inc. in writing.
Disclaimer of Warranty
THE USE OF THIS WEB SITE IS AT YOUR OWN RISK. NOVUS FRANCHISING INC. DOES NOT WARRANT THAT THE WEB SITE WILL OPERATE ERROR-FREE OR WITHOUT INTERRUPTION. THIS WEB SITE AND THE MATERIAL ARE PROVIDED ON AN 'AS IS' BASIS WITHOUT WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND. TO THE EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW NOVUS FRANCHISING INC. DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION, THE WARRANTY OF MERCHANTABILITY, NON-INFRINGEMENT OF THIRD PARTY RIGHTS, AND THE WARRANTY OF FITNESS FOR PARTICULAR PURPOSE. NOVUS FRANCHISING INC. DOES NOT REPRESENT OR WARRANT THE ACCURACY, RELIABILITY, COMPLETENESS, OR TIMELINESS OF THE MATERIAL ON THIS WEB SITE OR ON ANY SITES LINKED TO THIS WEB SITE NOR THE RESULTS TO BE OBTAINED FROM USING SUCH MATERIALS.
Limitation of Liability
IN NO EVENT SHALL NOVUS FRANCHISING INC. BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES WHATSOEVER INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, LOST PROFITS, OR DAMAGES RESULTING FROM LOST DATA OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION ARISING FROM THE USE OR INABILITY TO USE THIS WEB SITE AND THE MATERIAL, WHETHER BASED ON WARRANTY, CONTRACT, TORT, OR ANY OTHER LEGAL THEORY, AND WHETHER OR NOT NOVUS FRANCHISING INC. IS ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. THE LAWS OF SOME PROVINCES MAY NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF INCIDENTAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES OR THE EXCLUSION OF LIABILITY IN CERTAIN CIRCUMSTANCES, SO THE ABOVE LIMITATION OR EXCLUSION MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU.
User Transmissions
As a User, you are responsible for your own communications and are responsible for the consequences of their posting. You must not post or transmit to or from this Web Site any material that infringes on the copyright or any other intellectual property rights or on the privacy rights of others, nor post or transmit any unlawful, threatening, libelous, defamatory, scandalous, inflammatory, pornographic, or profane material, or any other material that could give rise to civil or criminal liability under the law. Any non-personal communications or materials that you transmit or post to this Web Site are considered to be non-confidential and non-proprietary unless otherwise indicated on this Web Site, and NOVUS Franchising Inc. and its affiliates shall have the right to use such materials for internal business purposes and for commercial purposes without further notice. Please refer to the Privacy Statement for details of how NOVUS Franchising Inc. collects, uses and discloses personal information that you may provide while using this Web Site.
General
All matters relating to your access to, or use of, this Web Site shall be governed by the laws of the Province of British Columbia and the federal laws of Canada applicable therein. You agree to submit to the jurisdiction of the courts of British Columbia in any legal action or proceeding relating to your access to, or use of, this Web Site. Should any provision of these Terms of Use be found to be illegal or unenforceable, all other provisions shall remain in full force and effect and be binding upon you.
The Novusglass.com Privacy Policy
Internet Privacy Statement
Respecting your privacy is important to NOVUS Franchising Inc. This Privacy Statement explains how NOVUS Franchising Inc. collects, uses and discloses the personal information you provide while using this Web Site.
Information Collection
When you browse this Web Site, personal information is not collected. Your IP address (the Internet address of your computer) is recorded so that we may know how you are using our Web Site. Your browser may also automatically provide us with information regarding the type of computer and operating system you are using. This information is used to monitor and improve our Web Site. This information is not linked back to you as an individual user.
We may request that you provide us with personal information, including your e-mail address, postal address and telephone number in order to provide quotes or respond to inquiries. If you are an insurance agent and wish to register on the Special Member area of this Web Site, we will require your personal information as set out in our site registration form. NOVUS Franchising Inc. administers the NOVUS Franchising Inc. residential policy program for insurers. Special Members who submit policy-holder information to us, are responsible for compliance with applicable privacy legislation in respect of personal information shared with us.
Information submitted through this Web Site will be stored and processed in Burnaby, British Columbia, Canada.
Information Use
Currently, we collect, use and disclose personal information submitted through this website for the purpose of contacting and corresponding with Users, responding to their inquiries, facilitating transactions with NOVUS Franchising Inc. and its affiliates and for related business purposes. In addition, unless you do not agree, we will use the personal information you provide to us to provide you with information about other NOVUS Franchising Inc. products and services. If you do not wish to receive such information, please let us know by e-mail at: support@novusglass.com. You may exercise this right to opt-out at any time.
Policy-holder information provided to us by Special Members for NOVUS Franchising Inc. is used to administer the Program and for claims purposes. NOVUS Franchising Inc. does not sell or trade, your personal information. We may disclose your personal information if we are permitted or required to do so by law or where it is required for the purposes of a corporate sale, acquisition, merger or re-organization.
Your Acceptance Of These Terms
By using this Web Site, you signify your agreement to this Privacy Statement. If you do not agree with this Privacy Statement, please do not use this Web Site. NOVUS Franchising Inc. reserves the right to change this Privacy Statement at any time. Any revisions will be posted on this Web Site and you should check this page periodically for changes.
More Information; Queries
NOVUS Franchising Inc. is committed to respecting your privacy and has implemented appropriate safeguards to protect your personal information. If you wish to request a summary of your personal information on record with us or if you wish to amend any inaccuracies or have other any other questions about this Privacy Statement, please contact our Manager, Personal Privacy, at support@novusglass.com.
